A Guide to the Weaver Orphan Home (Hampton, Va. ) Records, 1847-1978
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Weaver Orphan Home (Hampton, Va.) Records, 1847-1978
The Library of Virginia
51625
23.5 cubic feet (55 boxes) and 13 volumes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
THIS COLLECTION IS CURRENTLY UNAVAILABLE PENDING REVIEW BY THE OFFICE OF THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Reuben Price, Hampton.
Historical Information
William B. Weaver was born in Winton, Hertford County, North Carolina on 7 April 1852. He was the son of Willis Weaver (ca. 1814-1893) and Sally Weaver (ca. 1824-1894). Weaver attended Hampton Institute from 1872 to 1875. He then taught at various schools in North Carolina, Virginia, and Pennsylvania. In 1879, Weaver went to Gloucester County, Virginia, where he taught in the public schools for six years, including at Bethel School. On 1 September 1884, Weaver married Anna Bolden. She was born into slavery in 1859 in Cumberland County, Virginia. Following the Civil War, she and other family members moved North and settled in New York between Albany and Troy. She graduated from Albany High School in 1880. Bolden then went back to Virginia and taught at Bethel School where she met Weaver.
In 1888, Weaver and Thomas C. Walker (an 1883 graduate of Hampton) co-founded the Gloucester Agricultural and Industrial School in Cappahosic. Weaver left the school in 1900. The Weaver family then moved to Hampton, and in 1902 purchased 25 acres of land, and built a home the following year for the care of African-American orphans. The first children arrived on 12 August 1904. They also operated a school at the home until 1958. The Weaver Orphan Home was not state-supported. It operated through contributions from parents, social service organizations, welfare agencies, and private donations. In the early years, there were as many as 35 residents, but later attendance was around 20 children. The Home closed in 1965.
Rev. William B. Weaver died on 17 January 1929. Following his death, Anna B. Weaver continued to operate the Home with the assistance of her daughter Ruth Weaver Fagan (1898-1978) and her husband Spillman Fagan (1890-1973). The Fagans continued to run the Home for another 22 years following Anna B. Weaver's death on 16 September 1943.
Scope and Content
Records, 1847-1978, of the Weaver Orphan Home in Hampton, Virginia, which was operated from 1904 to 1965 by Rev. William B. Weaver (1852-1929) and his wife Anna (Bolden) Weaver (1859-1943), and later by their daughter Ruth (Weaver) Fagan (1898-1978) and her husband Spillman Fagan (1890-1973). In additon, there are records of the Gloucester Agricultural and Industrial School which Rev. Weaver co-founded, and papers of the Weaver, Bolden, and Fagan families.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I. Weaver Orphan Home Records.
II. Gloucester Agricultural and Industrial School Records.
III. Weaver-Bolden-Fagan Family Papers.
Contents List
- Series I. Weaver Orphan Home Records, 1901-1978., Extent: 42 boxes and 13 volumes. (Box 1-40, 54-55)
  The Weaver Orphan Home records include administrative records and resident files. The administrative records contain accounts and receipts, annual reports, applications for admission, bank statements and check registers, budgets, calendars, circulars, clippings, correspondence, donation records, inspection records, lists of residents, licenses, minutes of the Board of Trustees, newsletters, photographs and negatives, placement records, programs, records of charitable organizations, including the Community Chest and Peninsula United Fund, religious tracts, report cards and other school records, telephone logs, and visitor registers.
  The resident files contain information relating to the children who were placed in the Home, either by a parent or guardian or welfare agency. There are not files for every child who was a resident. The files that are extant include any or all of the following materials: applications, case information, discharge and placement records, correspondence from parents or guardians, relatives, courts, social service organizations, or the resident themself, birth certificates, photographs, health records, award certificates and receipts from social service agencies, announcements and invitations to graduations and weddings, and school records, including transcripts, exercises, report cards, disciplinary notices, certificates, and graduation programs. The files are arranged alphabetically by surname.
  - Administrative Records
    - Aberdeen School. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Aberdeen School - Notices and Thank You Letters. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Aberdeen School - Report Cards. (Box 1, Folder 3-8)
    - Account Book, 1947-1948. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Accounts and Receipts, 1909-1954. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Accounts and Receipts, 1955-1957. (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
    - Accounts and Receipts, 1958-1960. (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
    - Accounts and Receipts, 1961-1963. (Box 4, Folder 1-7)
    - Accounts and Receipts, 1964-1965. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
    - Address Book. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Addresses. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Anniversary Programs. (Box 5, Folder 6-7)
    - Annual Financial and Statistical Reports, 1943-1951. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports to the Board of Trustees. (Box 5, Folder 9-11)
    - Annual Reports - Virginia Department of Public Welfare, 1942, 1944. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Applications, 1904-1939. (Box 6, Folder 1-33)
    - Applications, 1940-1959. (Box 7, Folder 1-7)
    - Applications, undated. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Automobile. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Bank Books. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bank Statements, 1922, 1925-1959. (Box 8, Folder 3-10)
    - Bank Statements, 1960-1965. (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Barn, 1938. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bequests. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Board of Trustees - Lists of Names. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Broadsides/Circulars. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Brochures. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Budgets, 1948-1960. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Cain, Maizie Boone and Harris, Pattie (Teachers). (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Calendars, 1940, 1956, 1959-1961. (Box 9, Folder 10-14)
    - Card File, 1936. (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Carrington, Catherine (Teacher). (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Cash Expenses, 1929-1936. (Volume 1)
    - Cash Payments, 1935. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cash Payments, 1936-1945. (Volume 2)
    - Cash Payments, 1946. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cash Payments, 1947-1955. (Volume 3)
    - Cash Payments, 1956-1964. (Volume 4)
    - Cash Receipts, 1936-1955. (Volume 5)
    - Cash Receipts, 1939-1942. (Box 10, Folder 6-10)
    - Cash Receipts, 1945. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Cash Receipts, 1956-1966. (Volume 6)
    - Cash Receipts Book, 1929-1936. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1911-1951. (Box 10, Folder 13-16)
    - Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1952-1965. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Certificates - Sunday School. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Charter. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Check Registers, 1937-1943. (Box 11, Folder n/a)
    - Check Registers, 1943-1955. (Box 12, Folder n/a)
    - Check Registers, 1955-1965. (Box 13, Folder n/a)
    - Children's Homes - Conferences and Correspondence. (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
    - Children in the Home. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Childrens' Names and Ages. (Box 14, Folder 6-9)
    - Childrens' Names and Birthdays. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Childrens' Names and Placements, 1917-1926. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Childrens' Programs. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - The Christian Educator, February 1928. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - The Christian Worker, 1903-1908, 1914. (Box 15, Folder 3-9)
    - Christmas Gifts, 1956. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Church Records. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Church, Toney - Legacy. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Civics Class Notes. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Civil Defense Guide. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Clippings. (Box 15, Folder 15-17)
    - Collection Book, 1911-1917. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Community Chest, 1940-1944. (Box 15, Folder 19-23)
    - Community Chest, 1945-1953. (Box 16, Folder 1-9)
    - Community Chest, 1954-1956. (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
    - Community Chest (Hampton), 1944-1950. (Box 17, Folder 4-6)
    - Community Chest - Constitutions and By-Laws. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Community Chest - Radio and Newspaper. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Community Services Planning Council Volunteer Bureau. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Composition Book. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Contracts for Repairs, 1941-1945. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Cows and Horses. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1901, 1905-1915. (Box 17, Folder 13-23)
    - Correspondence, 1916-1947. (Box 18, Folder 1-30)
    - Correspondence, 1948-1965. (Box 19, Folder 1-15)
    - Correspondence - Department of Public Welfare. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - Trustees. (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, undated. (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Daily Expenses, 1911-1914, 1922. (Volume 7)
    - Deaths. (Box 19a, Folder 1)
    - Donations for Orphan Home and Mission Work, 1904-1906. (Box 19a, Folder 2)
    - Donations, 1908-1931. (Box 19a, Folder 3-6)
    - Donations, 1937-1939. (Box 19a, Folder 7)
    - Donations, 1943-1945. (Box 19a, Folder 8)
    - Donations, 1949-1965. (Box 19a, Folder 9-12)
    - Donations, no year. (Box 19a, Folder 13)
    - Drive Records, 1936-1940. (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Emergency Relief Administration. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Entry Book, 1904-1923. (Volume 8)
    - Entry and Receipt Book, 1904-1910. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Entry and Receipt Book, 1911-1916. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Entry and Receipt Book, 1926-1929. (Volume 9)
    - Expenditures - Orphan Home and Mission Work, 1901-1905. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Farm Records. (Box 20, Folder 7-8)
    - 50th Anniversary (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Fire Inspection Reports. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Fire Marshal Reports. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Food and Nutrition Information. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Forms (Blank). (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Frederick Douglass Stamps. (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Friends' Home for Children - Constitution and Bylaws. (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Fund for Heating System. (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Gifts, 1927. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Gifts, 1929. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Hampton Kiwanis Club. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Harmon Awards. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Health Publications. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Health Department Inspections. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Health Records. (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Historical Booklets. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - History of Weaver Orphan Home. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - HOPE and Fireside Schools. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hopson, Eugine. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - "How the Colored Race Can Help in the Problems Issuing From the War," 1919 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Howland, Emily - Legacy. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Hymns/Songs/Verses. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Instructions. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Invitations. (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Invitations - Military. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Jenkins Orphanage Institute (Charleston, SC). (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Keffie, Gladys (Teacher). (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Land Purchase, 1901-1902. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Le-Mac Nurseries. (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Lemons, Wiliam (Farm). (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Letters to Answers. (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Letters Written, 1936. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Letters Written, 1938-1943. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Letters Written, 1940. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Letters Written, 1946-1947. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Letters Written, 1952-1956. (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
    - Licensed Homes for Children. (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Licenses. (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Maps/Plats/Surveys. (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Memorandum Book. (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Minutes - Board of Trustees. (Box 22, Folder 17-19)
    - Miscellaneous. (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Names of Former Children. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - National Youth Administration Teachers (Hampton Institute). (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - "A Naturalist With MacMillan in the Arctic." (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Negatives. (Box 54, Folder n/a)
    - Negatives. (Box 55, Folder n/a)
    - Negro History. (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
    - Nelson, Laura (Matron). (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Notebook. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Orr, Doris (Teacher). (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Peninsula United Community Fund, 1957-1958. (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
    - Peninsula United Fund, 1959-1962. (Box 23, Folder 12-15)
    - Peninsula United Fund, 1963-1965. (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
    - Peninsula United Fund Agencies. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Peninsula United Fund - Annual Reports. (Box 24, Folder 6-8)
    - Peninsula Welfare Planning Council. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Photographs. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Photographs. (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Physicians' Certificates. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Postcards - Weaver Orphan Home. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Practice Teachers. (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Programs. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Public Welfare, Department of. (Box 25, Folder 7-8)
    - Radio Interview, 18 October 1950. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Ration Books. (Box 26, Folder 2-5)
    - Receipt Book Registers, 1906, 1919-1920, 1935-1946. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Religious Tracts. (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
    - Religious Tracts. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Reports on Examination, 1956-1964. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Reports/Statements of Facts, 1904-1926. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Rombo, Rose (Teacher). (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - School Exercises. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - School Records. (Box 27, Folder 6-7)
    - Scrapbook Pages - Washington and Lincoln. (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Sermon. (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Shaw, Ella Hare - Legacy. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - S. Mary's Home For Little Colored Boys (Baltimore). (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Sleicher, Lydia E. - Legacy. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Frances Virginia (Summer Teacher). (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Social Services, 1946-1949. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Speech - "Problems of the Child in Public School." (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - State Board of Education. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - State Department of Public Welfare. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - State Welfare Department - Monthly Reports, 1944. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - State Welfare Standards for Licensed Childrens Home Institutions. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Stationary. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Sunday School Exercises. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Superintendents and Orphan Workers Conference. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Supervisors and Teachers. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Taxes. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Telephone Calls, 1948-1952. (Box 28, Folder 7-15)
    - Telephone Calls, 1953-1958. (Box 29, Folder 1-13)
    - Telephone Calls, 1958-1965. (Box 30, Folder 1-11)
    - Treasurer's Book, 1911-1940. (Volume 11)
    - Trustees Minute Book, 1911-1928. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - United Community Fund - Agency Reports. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Conference of Social Work. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Conference of Social Work - District II. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Negro Baptist Childrens' Home, Petersburg. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Visitors Register, 1922-1929. (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Visitors Register, 1939-1952. (Volume 12)
    - Visitors Register, 1952-1963. (Volume 13)
    - Visitors Register, 1963-1965. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - The Weaver Home Bulletin, 1925-1926. (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Weaver Parental Aid Association. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Welfare and Institutions, Department of - Annual Reports, 1929-1948. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1960. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Willis, Sarah W. - Legacy. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Weaver Bros. Notes. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Weaver Orphan Home Showcase Unveiling, 20 March 1977. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Writing Exercises, 1909. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Y. H. Thomas Jr. High School. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Resident Files
    - Anderson, Herbert Hoover. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Arnold, Lee Walker. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Benthall, Elsie and Geneva and Inez and Harvey. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bess, Yvonne S. and Andrew Montrollas. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Bittle, Esther Louise. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Bland, Mary and Ruth and William and Calvin. (Box 33, Folder 6-7)
    - Bland, William Thomas. (Box 33, Folder 8-10)
    - Blount, Valeria and Felicia. (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Bluford, Lulu. (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Bowden, Delancy and David. (Box 33, Folder 13-15)
    - Bowles, Herbert and Eston Lee and Doris and Elouise. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Braxton, Vivian and Gloria and Brenda. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Brickhouse, Jacob and Walter and Cecil. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Brown, Junious and Rufus. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Viola and Laurie and Arnella and Celestine. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Burton, Peggy Elaine and Charles L. and Richard Lee. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Butler. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Butts, John. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Calloway, Annie Bell. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Edward. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Carter, James Arthur. (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Carter, James Henry. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Carter, Lena Blanton. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Carter, Lloyd. (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Chappell, Allen Sanford Harrison and Marcell Monroe. (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Christian, Richard. (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Cole, Grace and Mary. (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Copp, Nellie. (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Craddolph, Hayden. (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Crayton, Harry Frederick and Labarbara Mallette. (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Davis, Carrie. (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Davis, Floretia Mae and Lillian Rebecca. (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Davis, James Edward. (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Joseph and Robert. (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Davis, Perry Alexander. (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Day, James. (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Derell, Wyonna and Leroy. (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Doswell, Gertrude and Ernestine and Jesse Eugene and David. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Driver, Mabel and Bessie. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Edwards, Lillian Charlene and Charles. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Ellis, Robert and Grace and Evelyn. (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Ennis, Edna and Evelyn and Dorothy. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Fennell, Charles Augustus. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Fields, Coleman and Dorothy. (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Fisher, Ruth Elizabeth. (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Foster, James Melvin and William Earl. (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Gardner, Terry Lee. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Gates. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Gates, Martha and Charles and George. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Goodman, Jacquelin and Ella. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Graves, Edward Lee. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Green, Theodore. (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Gross, Lucretia Galindo. (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Harris, Dorothy. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Harris, James Martin. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Harris, Mary Odessa. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Haskins, Edith. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Haskins, James Bradshaw Jr. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Julius. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Holloway, Hethorn and William and Oliver. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Holmes, Grace. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Hooper, Larry and Norman. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Howard, Ernest Leslie and Paul Nicholas. (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Hunter, Leon. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Bennie Jr. and Gerry Lee. (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Lewis Munroe. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - James, William (Billy) and John H. Jr. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Jett, William and Mary. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Maybelle. (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Alonzo Bernell Byrd. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Andrew Thomas. (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Jones, Elizabeth. (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Jones, Harvey and Elsie and Kate. (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Jones, James Allen. (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Jones, Leon and Ricardo. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Jones, Leroy Jr. and Gilbert and Walter. (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Jones, Myrtle. (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Jones, William Joshua and Smith, Josie Alberta. (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Jones, Willie and Charles and Eva Celestine. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Jordan, Ralph Cooper and Rose Marie. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Killman, Audrey Mae. (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Knox, Sherman and Floyd and Philander and Leroy. (Box 37, Folder 4-7)
    - Lane, Darnell and James. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Lassiter, Pauline and Blanche and Mary. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Lewis, Mary and Henry and Rollie. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Lowry, Madison and John. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Luton, Bernard Alfonso and Joyce. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Madison, Zoenna. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Manley, Ronald and Richard. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Matthews, Edward Thomas. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - McCougan, Leola Helen. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Milo, James Curtis. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Mitchell, Rodney. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Moore, Gladys. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Mozee, Lelia D. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Norfleet, Albert Lee Jones. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Norfleet, Stanley and Kerry. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Northcutt, Gloria Ann and George. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Oliver, Fred Lee. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Parham, Annie and Lucile and Glendora and Mary. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Parker, Florence Elizabeth. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Payne, Percy and Arnetha and James and Robert. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Peoples, Edward. (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Perry, Vera May. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Pitt, Roger. (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Pratt, Ida and Mary. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Purdy, Dorothy Mae. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Randall, Freddie. (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Reeves, Lavinia. (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Riddick, Vivian and Saunders. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Robinson, William. (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Robinson, Yvone and Juanita and Ulysses. (Box 38, Folder 25)
    - Russell, Deloris and Raleigh and Evelyn. (Box 38, Folder 26)
    - Sawyer, Catherine. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Scott, Robert and Ruth. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Scott, Wilbur. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Sharp, Jack and Nick and Pearl. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Sheffy. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Simms, Deloris and Clarence and Rosemarie. (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Slaughter, Catherine Francine. (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Small, William and Sharon. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Aleta and Carol and Emma and Lottie and Earl. (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Benjamin and Elfreda and William. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Josie and Vivian Earline. (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Leon and Calvert. (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Stewart, Garland. (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Stoakley, Norman and Ermon and Frances and William. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Strange, Margaret and Clara and Susie. (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Sullivan, Shirley and Junius. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Sykes. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Tanner, James. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Taylor, Harry. (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Thomas, Albertha and Clarence. (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Harry. (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Thomas, Mose and David and Stanley and Steven. (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Toliver, Rudolph and Leon and William and Leonard and Leon and Anthony. (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Triniar, Sam. (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Trower, Jeanette. (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Turner, Verna and Adelle and Sherman. (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - Walker, Barbara Magnolia. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Walker, Caroline Elaine. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Walker, Caroline Elaine. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Waller, Barbara and Nina and Gloria and Spencer and Estelle and Elenora. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Washington, Susie and Ira and Mariah and Burt. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Watkins, Maggie. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Watson, Oscar and James. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Weaver. (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Weaver, Fred. (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Wheeler, Beatrice Brown. (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Whitaker, Bertha and Aaron and Earley. (Box 40, Folder 10)